(Leonard:)Why don't I just start?
(Leonard:)Sometimes people have trouble
accepting accolades...
(Leonard:)...if on a subconscious level,
they don't feel they deserve them.
(Leonard:)Do you think maybe
that's what's happening here?
(Sheldon:)Really, Leonard?
You just going to try to recycle Adler's
doctrine of the inferiority complex?
(Sheldon:)I could probably get that
from the woman at Ralph's.
(Sheldon:)And she'd let me taste some pieces
of cheese for free.
(Leonard:)But it could be part of your problem.
Let me give you an example.
When I was 8, I won a ribbon
at the science fair for my project...
(Leonard:)...Do Lima Beans Grow Better
to Classical Music.
(Leonard:)But my mother pointed out
that it was just a rehash...
(Leonard:)...of my brother's earlier...
(Leonard:)...Do Lima Beans Grow Worse
to Rock 'n' Roll.
(Leonard:)I felt so guilty
I gave the ribbon back.
(Sheldon:)And how did that make you feel?